quiz_data = [
    {
    "question": "Which of these is an attack vector?",
    "correct_answer": "Malware",
    "options": [
        "Malware",
        "A weak password",
        "Script kiddie",
        "Loss of intellectual property"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What is the process that occurs when the Session layer removes the header from the data sent by the Transport layer?",
    "correct_answer": "De-encapsulation",
    "options": [
        "Encapsulation",
        "Packet unwrapping",
        "De-encapsulation",
        "Payloading"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Purchasing insurance is a form of what type of risk response?",
    "correct_answer": "Transfer",
    "options": [
        "Transfer",
        "Avoid",
        "Mitigate",
        "Accept"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What port does SMTP use?",
    "correct_answer": "25",
    "options": [
        "37",
        "25",
        "27",
        "53"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What technology ensures that an operating system allocates separate memory spaces used by each application on a system?",
    "correct_answer": "Process isolation",
    "options": [
        "Abstraction",
        "Layering",
        "Data hiding",
        "Process isolation"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "David recently signed a contract with an alternate data processing facility that will provide his company with space in the event of a disaster. The facility includes HVAC, power, and communication circuits but no hardware. What type of facility is being used?",
    "correct_answer": "Cold site",
    "options": [
        "Warm site",
        "Mobile site",
        "Cold site",
        "Hot site"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What port does IMAP use?",
    "correct_answer": "143",
    "options": [
        "119",
        "123",
        "143",
        "161"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What Kerberos service generates a new ticket and session keys and sends them to the client?",
    "correct_answer": "TGS",
    "options": [
        "KDC",
        "TGT",
        "AS",
        "TGS"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What port does ISO-TSAP operate on?",
    "correct_answer": "102",
    "options": [
        "102",
        "119",
        "110",
        "97"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What level of RAID is known as disk striping?",
    "correct_answer": "RAID 0",
    "options": [
        "RAID 1",
        "RAID 0",
        "RAID 5",
        "RAID 10"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Which of the books in the Rainbow Series deals with Trusted Computer Evaluation?",
    "correct_answer": "Orange Book",
    "options": [
        "Blue book",
        "Tan Book",
        "Orange Book",
        "Green Book"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What service runs off port 137?",
    "correct_answer": "NetBIOS-ns",
    "options": [
        "EPMAP",
        "NetBIOS-ns",
        "IMAP",
        "NetBIOS-ssn"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Johnny is designing a backup system and wants to implement RAID level 5 for his system. What is the minimum number of physical hard disks he can use to build this system?",
    "correct_answer": "3",
    "options": [
        "1",
        "5",
        "3",
        "2"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "What service runs off port 139?",
    "correct_answer": "NetBIOS-ssn",
    "options": [
        "EPMAP",
        "NetBIOS-ns",
        "NetBIOS-ssn",
        "IMAP"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Microsoftâ€™s STRIDE threat assessment framework uses six categories for threats: Spoofing, Tampering, Repudiation, Information Disclosure, Denial of Service, and Elevation of Privilege. If a penetration tester is able to modify audit logs, what STRIDE categories best describe this issue?",
    "correct_answer": "Repudiation and Tampering",
    "options": [
        "Tampering and Information Disclosure",
        "Elevation of Privilege and Tampering",
        "Repudiation and Denial of Service",
        "Repudiation and Tampering"
    ]
},
]
